Technical University of British Columbia fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
- Board of Governors records, 1995 - 2002; F-177-2; 2.50 m of textual records 26 photographs 88 negatives 1 contact sheet; Physical description: 1 photograph located in F-177-2-1-0-11 Physical description: 2 photographs located in F-177-2-1-0-12 Physical description: 21 photographs located in F-177-
  - Board minutes and supporting papers, 1997 - 2002; F-177-2-3; 1.06 m of textual records
    - Board of Governors meeting, January 26, 1998, vol. 2, F-177-2-3-0-96 (Archival box - standard 177-85)
    - Board of Governors meeting, January 26, 1998, vol. 3, F-177-2-3-0-97 (Archival box - standard 177-85)
    - Board of Governors meeting, December 12, 1997, F-177-2-3-0-98 (Archival box - standard 177-85)
  - Committees of the Board records, 1998 - 2002; F-177-2-4; 99 cm of textual records
    Sub-series consists of records relating to Board of Governors committees. Activities, events and topics documented include committee meetings and membership, as well as the specific activities and responsibilities of each committee. Records include terms of reference and membership lists; agendas, minutes, and supporting papers; correspondence and reports; budgets and financial statements; press releases; and contracts.
    - Committees of the Board - general records, 1998 - 1999; F-177-2-4-1; 1 cm of textual records
      Sub-series consists of lists of Board of Governors committees and voting and non-voting committee members.
      - Committees of the Board, 1998 - 1999; F-177-2-4-1-1 (Archival box - standard 177-86)
    - Academic Planning Board records, 1998 - 2002; F-177-2-4-2; 36 cm of textual records; Technical University of British Columbia. Board of Governors. Academic Planning Board
      The Academic Planning Board (APB) was a committee of the Board of Governors created on May 8, 1998 in response to the Canadian Association of University Teachers (CAUT) and Confederation of University Faculty Associations of BC (CUFA) boycott. It was responsible for dealing with learning and research function issues, the creation of academic goals and priorities, and the establishment of short- and long-term academic plans. The APB was also able to pass motions pertaining to academic freedom and employment issues. It was dissolved on July 5, 2002.
      Sub-sub-series consists of records relating to meetings of the Academic Planning Board. Records include minutes and supporting papers and a reference manual.
      The material was arranged according to the original filing system of the creator. Files are arranged chronologically.
      - Academic Planning Board meeting - February 4, 2002, F-177-2-4-2-1 (Archival box - standard 177-86)
      - Academic Planning Board meeting - November 21, 2001, F-177-2-4-2-2 (Archival box - standard 177-86)
      - Academic Planning Board meeting - September 26, 2001, vol. 1, F-177-2-4-2-3 (Archival box - standard 177-86)
      - Academic Planning Board meeting - September 26, 2001, vol. 2, F-177-2-4-2-4 (Archival box - standard 177-86)
      - Academic Planning Board meeting - July 25, 2001, vol. 1, F-177-2-4-2-5 (Archival box - standard 177-86)
      - Academic Planning Board meeting - July 25, 2001, vol. 2, F-177-2-4-2-6 (Archival box - standard 177-86)
      - Academic Planning Board meeting - May 23, 2001, vol. 1, F-177-2-4-2-7 (Archival box - standard 177-86)
      - Academic Planning Board meeting - May 23, 2001, vol. 2, F-177-2-4-2-8 (Archival box - standard 177-86)
      - Academic Planning Board meeting - March 21, 2001, F-177-2-4-2-9 (Archival box - standard 177-86)
      - Academic Planning Board meeting - January 30, 2001, F-177-2-4-2-10 (Archival box - standard 177-86)
      - Academic Planning Board meeting - December 6, 2000, F-177-2-4-2-11 (Archival box - standard 177-86)
      - Academic Planning Board - reference manual, November 2000, F-177-2-4-2-12 (Archival box - standard 177-87)
      - Academic Planning Board meeting - October 25, 2000, vol. 1, F-177-2-4-2-13 (Archival box - standard 177-87)
      - Academic Planning Board meeting - October 25, 2000, vol. 2, F-177-2-4-2-14 (Archival box - standard 177-87)
      - Academic Planning Board meeting - October 25, 2000, vol. 3, F-177-2-4-2-15 (Archival box - standard 177-87)
      - Academic Planning Board meeting - September 6, 2000, F-177-2-4-2-16 (Archival box - standard 177-87)
      - Academic Planning Board meeting - July 5, 2000, vol. 1, F-177-2-4-2-17 (Archival box - standard 177-87)
      - Academic Planning Board meeting - July 5, 2000, vol. 2, F-177-2-4-2-18 (Archival box - standard 177-87)
      - Academic Planning Board meeting - July 5, 2000, vol. 3, F-177-2-4-2-19 (Archival box - standard 177-87)
      - Academic Planning Board meeting - March 15, 2000, F-177-2-4-2-20 (Archival box - standard 177-87)
      - Academic Planning Board meeting - January 19, 2000, F-177-2-4-2-21 (Archival box - standard 177-87)
      - Academic Planning Board meeting - October 6, 1999, vol. 1, F-177-2-4-2-22 (Archival box - standard 177-88)
      - Academic Planning Board meeting - October 6, 1999, vol. 2, F-177-2-4-2-23 (Archival box - standard 177-88)
      - Academic Planning Board meeting - May 26, 1999, vol. 1, F-177-2-4-2-24 (Archival box - standard 177-88)
      - Academic Planning Board meeting - May 26, 1999, vol. 2, F-177-2-4-2-25 (Archival box - standard 177-88)
      - Academic Planning Board meeting - March 3, 1999, vol. 1, F-177-2-4-2-26 (Archival box - standard 177-88)
      - Academic Planning Board meeting - March 3, 1999, vol. 2, F-177-2-4-2-27 (Archival box - standard 177-88)
      - Academic Planning Board meeting - January 14, 1999, vol. 1, F-177-2-4-2-28 (Archival box - standard 177-88)
      - Academic Planning Board meeting - January 14, 1999, vol. 2, F-177-2-4-2-29 (Archival box - standard 177-88)
      - Academic Planning Board meeting - November 16, 1998, F-177-2-4-2-30 (Archival box - standard 177-88)
    - Audit Committee records, 1998 - 2001; F-177-2-4-3; 7 cm of textual records; Technical University of British Columbia. Board of Governors. Audit Committee
      Sub-sub-series consists of records relating to the activities of the Audit Committee, sometimes also referred to as the Finance and Audit Committee. Activities, events and topics documented include Committee meetings, budget preparation, and correspondence with the Auditor General's Office. Records include terms of reference; minutes and supporting papers; correspondence; financial statements; and an information package.
      The arrangement was provided by the archivist. Committee meeting files are arranged chronologically.
      Technical University of British Columbia. Board of Governors. Audit Committee
      - Finance and Audit Committee - terms of reference, 1999; F-177-2-4-3-1 (Archival box - standard 177-89)
      - Correspondence - Office of the Auditor General, 2000; F-177-2-4-3-2 (Archival box - standard 177-89)
      - Audited financial statements, March 31, 2001, F-177-2-4-3-3 (Archival box - standard 177-89)
      - Audit Committee meeting, June 21, 2001, F-177-2-4-3-4 (Archival box - standard 177-89)
      - Audit Committee meeting, June 20, 2000, F-177-2-4-3-5 (Archival box - standard 177-89)
      - March 31, 2000 - audited financial statements, F-177-2-4-3-6 (Archival box - standard 177-89)
      - Auditor general information package, December 23, 1999, 1999 - 2000; F-177-2-4-3-7 (Archival box - standard 177-89)
      - Audit Committee meeting, December 7, 1999, F-177-2-4-3-8 (Archival box - standard 177-89)
      - Audit Committee meeting, July 30, 1999, F-177-2-4-3-9 (Archival box - standard 177-89)
      - Audited financial statements, March 31, 1999, F-177-2-4-3-10 (Archival box - standard 177-89)
      - Finance and Audit Committee - University financial statements (1997/1998), F-177-2-4-3-11 (Archival box - standard 177-89)
      - [Budget statements and projections, 1997/98 to 1999/2000], 1998; F-177-2-4-3-12 (Archival box - standard 177-89)
    - Business and Finance Committee records, 1998 - 2002; F-177-2-4-4; 28 cm of textual records; Technical University of British Columbia. Board of Governors. Business and Finance Committee
      Sub-sub-series consists of records relating to the Business and Finance Commitee. Activities, events and topics documented include Committee meetings and membership, and University budgets and financial issues. Records include minutes and supporting papers; correspondence; budgets and financial statements; and membership lists.
      Technical University of British Columbia. Board of Governors. Business and Finance Committee
      - Business and Finance Committee - membership list, 1999; F-177-2-4-4-1 (Archival box - standard 177-89)
      - Business and Finance Committee - general, 1998; F-177-2-4-4-2 (Archival box - standard 177-89)
      - Business and Finance Committee meeting, August 8, 2001, F-177-2-4-4-3 (Archival box - standard 177-89)
      - Business and Finance Committee meeting, June 6, 2001, F-177-2-4-4-4 (Archival box - standard 177-89)
      - Business and Finance Committee meeting, May 25, 2001, F-177-2-4-4-5 (Archival box - standard 177-89)
      - Business and Finance Committee meeting, May 17, 2001, F-177-2-4-4-6 (Archival box - standard 177-89)
      - Business and Finance Committee meeting, May 8, 2001, 2002; F-177-2-4-4-7 (Archival box - standard 177-89)
      - Business and Finance Committee ProjectOne Update, May 8, 2001, F-177-2-4-4-8 (Archival box - standard 177-89)
      - Business and Finance Committee meeting, March 8, 2001, F-177-2-4-4-9 (Archival box - standard 177-89)
      - Business and Finance Committee meeting, February 2, 2001, F-177-2-4-4-10 (Archival box - standard 177-89)
      - Business and Finance Committee meeting, January 19, 2001, F-177-2-4-4-11 (Archival box - standard 177-89)
      - Business and Finance Committee meeting, December 7, 2000, vol. 1, F-177-2-4-4-12 (Archival box - standard 177-90)
      - Business and Finance Committee meeting, December 7, 2000, vol. 2, F-177-2-4-4-13
      - Business and Finance Committee meeting, October 19, 2000, F-177-2-4-4-14 (Archival box - standard 177-90)
      - Business and Finance Committee meeting, August 18, 2000, F-177-2-4-4-15 (Archival box - standard 177-90)
      - Business and Finance Committee - budget preparation update, June 29, 2000, F-177-2-4-4-16 (Archival box - standard 177-90)
      - Business and Finance Committee meeting, January 31, 2000, F-177-2-4-4-17 (Archival box - standard 177-90)
      - TechBC budget 1999/2000, 1998 - 1999; F-177-2-4-4-18 (Archival box - standard 177-90)
      - Business and Finance Committee meeting, August 25, 1999, F-177-2-4-4-19 (Archival box - standard 177-90)
      - Business and Finance Committee meeting, May 21, 1999, F-177-2-4-4-20 (Archival box - standard 177-90)
      - Business and Finance Committee meeting, May 21, 1999, F-177-2-4-4-21 (Archival box - standard 177-90)
      - Business and Finance Committee meeting, April 19, 1999, F-177-2-4-4-22 (Archival box - standard 177-90)
      - Business and Finance Committee - minutes of meetings, 1998; F-177-2-4-4-23 (Archival box - standard 177-90)
    - Executive Committee records, 1998 - 2001; F-177-2-4-5; 7 cm of textual records; Technical University of British Columbia. Board of Governors. Executive Committee
      Sub-sub-series consists of records relating to the activities of the Executive Committee of the Board. Records include minutes and supporting papers, and a membership list.
      Technical University of British Columbia. Board of Governors. Executive Committee
      - Executive Committee - membership list, 2001; F-177-2-4-5-1 (Archival box - standard 177-90)
      - Executive Committee meeting, August 31, 2001, F-177-2-4-5-2 (Archival box - standard 177-90)
      - Executive Committee meeting, July 31, 2001, F-177-2-4-5-3 (Archival box - standard 177-91)
      - Executive Committee meeting, July 3, 2001, F-177-2-4-5-4 (Archival box - standard 177-91)
      - Executive Committee meeting, June 21, 2001, F-177-2-4-5-5 (Archival box - standard 177-91)
      - Executive Committee meeting, June 15, 2001, F-177-2-4-5-6 (Archival box - standard 177-91)
      - Executive Committee meeting, December 18, 2000, F-177-2-4-5-7 (Archival box - standard 177-91)
      - Executive Committee meeting, July 27, 2000, F-177-2-4-5-8 (Archival box - standard 177-91)
      - Executive Committee meeting, June 29, 2000, F-177-2-4-5-9 (Archival box - standard 177-91)
      - Executive Committee meeting, June 27, 2000, F-177-2-4-5-10 (Archival box - standard 177-91)
      - Executive Committee meeting, December 20, 1999, 1999 - 2000; F-177-2-4-5-11 (Archival box - standard 177-91)
      - Executive Committee meeting, December 1, 1999, 1999 - 2000; F-177-2-4-5-12 (Archival box - standard 177-91)
      - Executive Committee meeting, October 1, 1999, F-177-2-4-5-13 (Archival box - standard 177-91)
      - Executive Committee - minutes of meetings, 1998 - 1999; F-177-2-4-5-14 (Archival box - standard 177-91)
    - Human Resources Committee records, 1998 - 2001; F-177-2-4-6; 11 cm of textual records; Technical University of British Columbia. Board of Governors. Human Resources Committee
      Sub-sub-series consists of records relating to the activities of the Human Resources Committee, originally named the Employee Relations Committee. Includes also some records pertaining to meetings of the TechBC Pension Committee and the Senior Compensation Committee. Records include minutes and supporting papers, and a membership list.
      Technical University of British Columbia. Board of Governors. Employee Relations Committee; Technical University of British Columbia. Board of Governors. Human Resources Committee; Technical University of British Columbia. Pension Committee; Technical University of British Columbia. Board of Governors. Senior Compensation Committee
      - TechBC Pension Committee - miscellaneous documents, 1999 - 2001; F-177-2-4-6-1 (Archival box - standard 177-91)
      - Human Resources Committee meeting, November 20, 2001, F-177-2-4-6-2 (Archival box - standard 177-91)
      - Human Resources Committee meeting, October 3, 2001, F-177-2-4-6-3 (Archival box - standard 177-91)
      - Human Resources Committee meeting, August 8, 2001, F-177-2-4-6-4 (Archival box - standard 177-91)
      - Human Resources Committee meeting, June 29, 2001, F-177-2-4-6-5 (Archival box - standard 177-91)
      - Human Resources Committee meeting, June 6, 2001, F-177-2-4-6-6 (Archival box - standard 177-91)
      - Human Resources Committee, May 15, 2001 - SERP update, F-177-2-4-6-7 (Archival box - standard 177-91)
      - Human Resources Committee meeting, February 7, 2001, F-177-2-4-6-8 (Archival box - standard 177-91)
      - Human Resources Committee meeting, November 29, 2000, F-177-2-4-6-9 (Archival box - standard 177-91)
      - Human Resources Committee meeting, November 17, 2000, F-177-2-4-6-10 (Archival box - standard 177-91)
      - Human Resources Committee meeting, September 13, 2000, F-177-2-4-6-11 (Archival box - standard 177-91)
      - Human Resources Committee meeting, June 28, 2000, F-177-2-4-6-12 (Archival box - standard 177-91)
      - Human Resources Committee meeting, July 12, 2000, F-177-2-4-6-13 (Archival box - standard 177-91)
      - Human Resources Committee meeting, May 24, 2000, F-177-2-4-6-14 (Archival box - standard 177-91)
      - Senior Compensation Committee meeting, May 5, 2000, F-177-2-4-6-15 (Archival box - standard 177-91)
      - Human Resources Committee meeting, April 12, 2000, F-177-2-4-6-16 (Archival box - standard 177-91)
      - Human Resources Committee meeting, March 9, 2000, F-177-2-4-6-17 (Archival box - standard 177-92)
      - Human Resources Committee meeting, December 15, 1999, F-177-2-4-6-18 (Archival box - standard 177-92)
      - Human Resources Committee meeting, November 30, 1999, F-177-2-4-6-19 (Archival box - standard 177-92)
      - Human Resources Committee meeting, October 21, 1999, F-177-2-4-6-20 (Archival box - standard 177-92)
      - Human Resources Committee meeting, July 29, 1999, F-177-2-4-6-21 (Archival box - standard 177-92)
      - Human Resources Committee - minutes of meeting - miscellaneous, 1998 - 1999; F-177-2-4-6-22 (Archival box - standard 177-92)
      - Employee Relations Committee - membership list, 1998; F-177-2-4-6-23 (Archival box - standard 177-92)
      - Employee Relations Committee - general, 1999; F-177-2-4-6-24 (Archival box - standard 177-92)
    - Presidential Search Committee records, 2000 - 2001; F-177-2-4-7; 1 cm of textual records; Technical University of British Columbia. Board of Governors. Presidential Search Committee
      Sub-sub-series consists of records relating to the activities of the Presidential Search Committee, which was created in the fall of 2000 to select a successor to Bernard Sheehan. Records include terms of reference; membership lists; correspondence; press releases; a contract; and a curriculum vitae.
      Technical University of British Columbia. Board of Governors. Presidential Search Committee
      - Presidential Search Committee correspondence, 2000 - 2001; F-177-2-4-7-1 (Archival box - standard 177-92)
      - Presidential Search 2000/2001, F-177-2-4-7-2 (Archival box - standard 177-92)
      - Jean Watters contract, 2001; F-177-2-4-7-3 (Archival box - standard 177-92)
    - Senior Compensation Committee records, 1999 - 2001; F-177-2-4-8; 6 cm of textual records; Technical University of British Columbia. Board of Governors. Senior Compensation Committee
      Sub-sub-series consists of records relating to the activities of the Senior Compensation Committee. Activities, events and topics documented include Committee meetings, as well as Presidential objectives, annual reports and contracts. Records include minutes and supporting papers; reports and correspondence; and contracts.
      Technical University of British Columbia. Board of Governors. Senior Compensation Committee
      - Executive compensation - general, 2001; F-177-2-4-8-1 (Archival box - standard 177-92)
      - Senior Compensation Committee meeting, December 12, 2001, F-177-2-4-8-2 (Archival box - standard 177-92)
      - Senior Compensation Committee meeting, October 3, 2001, F-177-2-4-8-3 (Archival box - standard 177-92)
      - President's contract, 2000 - 2001; F-177-2-4-8-4 (Archival box - standard 177-92)
      - Senior Compensation Committee meeting, July 25, 2001, F-177-2-4-8-5 (Archival box - standard 177-92)
      - President's 2001 annual report - BSS, 13 July 2001; F-177-2-4-8-6 (Archival box - standard 177-92)
      - President's objectives 2001, F-177-2-4-8-7 (Archival box - standard 177-92)
      - Senior Compensation Committee meeting, March 1, 2001, F-177-2-4-8-8 (Archival box - standard 177-92)
      - Senior Compensation Committee meeting, February 7, 2001, vol. 1, 2000 - 2001; F-177-2-4-8-9 (Archival box - standard 177-92)
      - Senior Compensation Committee meeting, February 7, 2001, vol. 2, 2000 - 2001; F-177-2-4-8-10 (Archival box - standard 177-92)
      - President's objectives 2000, F-177-2-4-8-11 (Archival box - standard 177-92)
      - Senior Compensation Committee meeting, January 24, 2001, 2000; F-177-2-4-8-12 (Archival box - standard 177-92)
      - President's objectives 1999 [and 2000], 1999 - 2000; F-177-2-4-8-13 (Archival box - standard 177-92)
      - Senior Compensation Committee meeting, November 24, 1999, F-177-2-4-8-14 (Archival box - standard 177-92)
      - Senior Compensation Committee - minutes of meetings, 1999; F-177-2-4-8-15 (Archival box - standard 177-92)
    - University Review Committee, 2000 - 2001; F-177-2-4-9; 1 cm of textual records; Technical University of British Columbia. Board of Governors. University Review Committee
      Sub-sub-series consists of records relating to the activities and composition of the University Review Committee. Records include correspondence, membership lists, and a course outline.
      Technical University of British Columbia. Board of Governors. University Review Committee
      - University Review Committee membership, 2000; F-177-2-4-9-1 (Archival box - standard 177-92)
      - University Review Committee miscellaneous, 2000 - 2001; F-177-2-4-9-2 (Archival box - standard 177-92)
      - Administrative justice course, 2001; F-177-2-4-9-3 (Archival box - standard 177-92)